Barrett, Richard Sears Papers 6255
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Richard Sears Barrett Papers
1976-1997
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Barrett, Richard Sears
6255
55 cubic feet
55 linear ft.
Papers, case files.
6269045
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, August 06, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Psychology, Industrial--United States; Discrimination in employment--United States; Employee selection--United States; Employment tests--United States; Employment tests--Law and legislation--United States; Barrett, Richard S., 1924-
6269045
- Case Files: Action Travail - Alverez. (Box 1)
  - Action Travail OES Femmes (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adams vs General tire (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Addison U Nassau County (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alifaro v Suber (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Afro Americans v duck (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AFSCME v Hurley (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Akron FD (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Allen v. Alabama State Board of Ed. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Allen v Mobile (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Isabelo Alvarez et al. v City of Philadelphia (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Case Files: Birmingham - Bridgeport Guardians. (Box 2)
  - Birmingham Reverse Disc (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Bishop v. City of Greensboro (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Black (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - boles v Union Camp (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bradley v SOA Department of Public safety (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bradley v State Alaska (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bravo (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bridgeport firebirds (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bridgeport guardians v Bridgeport (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Case Files: Bridgeport Guardians (cont'd) - Bronze Shield. (Box 3)
  - Bridgeport Guardians v Bridgeport PD (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bridgeport Guardians + Smith Bridgeport (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bridgeport 1989 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bronze shield v NJ Civil Service (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Case Files: Burns - Chance. (Box 4)
  - Chance v Board of Examiners (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Caufield v Board of Ed (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Casaro v Beecher (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Capers v Lirr (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Castro v Beecher (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Caron Scott County (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Canada (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Byrd v Ibew (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - burns v Georgia (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Case Files: Chicago Firefighters - Colbert. (Box 5)
  - Chicago Fire, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Chicago (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Cohen vs Miami (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Colbert v H-K Corp. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Case Files: Columbus Police Dept. - Contreras. (Box 6)
  - Columbus PD (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Contreras v Bulger (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Case Files: Contreras - Crockett. (Box 7)
  - (Image) Contreras v. US Postal Service (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - High Priority Contreras v. US Postal Service (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Crocket v Tuscon (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Case Files: Crocker - Cuesta. (Box 8)
  - Croker V Boeing Vertol (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Crocket vs VA Folding in a Box (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Crocket v VA Folding (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Underwood V OCA (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - DC FD (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Case Files: Cuesta - Davis. (Box 9)
  - SUNY OF et al. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Insurance (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Cuesta et al. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Culpepper U Alabama Gas (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Davis v Washington (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Case Files: Delgato - Detroit Police Dept.. (Box 10)
  - Delgado v Penna Bd of Law Examiners (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Detroit DD (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Detroit POA v Detroit (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Case Files: Detroit Police Dept. (cont'd) - District of Columbia Fire Dept.. (Box 11)
  - DC FD (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Detroit Police Officers v Young (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - District 47 v Philadelphia (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Douglas v Hampton (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Douglas v Hampton (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Dreher v St Josephs Min. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Duhon v Goodyear Tire (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Case Files: District of Columbia Fire Dept. (cont'd). (Box 12)
  - DC Data: Faxes and Results, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - DC Data: Program Info, Demographics, and Frequency, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - DC Data: Scatter Plots and Cross Variation, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - DC Data: Multiple R., Cluster+ FA, and Results of ADM, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - DC Data: Reliability and Impact, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Office of the DC Auditor: Review of Negotiated Services Contracts Between DC and the Test Development Committee, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Agreement Between the Government of DC and the Technical Development Committee (Part 1), 1991 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Agreement Between the Government of DC and the Technical Development Committee (Part 2), 1991 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Agreement Between the Government of DC and the Technical Development Committee (Part 3), 1991 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - US District Court, DC: Hammon vs. Barry CA: 84-0903 (CRR), Byrne vs. Coleman CA: 85-0782, USA vs. DC CA: 85-9797, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - US District Court, DC: Rudder vs. DC Civil No. 92-2881 (CRR), 1995 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Comments on Proposed N.S. Contract No. 7095-AA-NS-0-7-LR Between D.C. and Barrett, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Motions and Decisions (89) Hammon vs. Barry CA:84-0903 (CRR), Byrne vs. Coleman CA: 85-0782, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Notes and Memos, DC (88), Hammon vs. Barry, Byrne vs. Coleman, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Invoices and Exchanges Regarding Hammon vs Barry, Byrne vs Coleman, 1987-1990 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Allen vs. District of Columbia CA: 92-0555 (CRR), 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Hammon vs. District of Columbia CA: 84-0903, 1985-1989 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Case Files: District of Columbia Fire Dept. (cont'd). (Box 13)
  - DC Firefighter (DCFD) Misc. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - DC Fire Department Misc. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Transcript of OHR Hearings: Testimony of Weiss, Von Rijn, and Devine, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Report of the Validity of Examinations for Sergeant, Lieutenant, and Captain in the Fire Department of the District of Columbia, 1976, 1980, 1982, 1976-1985 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Job Analysis of Entry Level Firefighting in the DCFD: Supervisory Perception of Entry Level Job, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Job Analysis of Entry Level Firefighting: A Comparison of DC Firefighters and a Nationwide Sample, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Job Analysis of Entry Level Firefighting in the DCFD: A Duty/Task Approach, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Job Analysis of Entry Level Firefighting in the DCFD: Administration and Results of the Position Analysis Questionnaire, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Development of a Written Test of Cognitive Abilities for Entry Into the DCFD: The Task-Ability-Test Linkage Procedure, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Interview Transcript Including Exhibits and Index (Rudder vs DC), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Rudder vs. DC: Declaration, Amended Complaint, and Disposition of Paul Hoffman (Part 1), 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Rudder vs. DC: Deposition of Paul Hoffman (Part 2) and Statements, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Rudder vs. DC: Letters, Statements, and Notes (Misc.), 1991-1995 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Rudder vs. DC: Letters, Statements and Notes (Misc.), 1991-1995 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Materials Related to DCFD Firefighter Tests, 1980-1995 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Criterion-Related Validity Research Base for the DC Firefighter Test, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Reading Ease Level of DCFD Written Materials Required for Entry Level Job Performance, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Validity of Test 21 for Selection of Entry Level Firefighters in the DCFD, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Psychometric Support for Test Item-Type Linkage to Six Ability Constructs Measured in the Entrance Exam for the DCFD, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - DCFD Job Analysis Information, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - DCFD Firefighter Promotional Process Written Exam Response Analysis, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - DCFD Order Book and Written Test, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - DCFD Written Tests and Development Sample, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Case Files: EEOC. (Box 14)
  - EEUC U Atlas Paper Box (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - EEUC U Atlas (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - EEOC U Burlington Northern (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Case Files: EEOC (cont'd) - Ellis. (Box 15)
  - EEOC U Duquesne Power + Light (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - EEOC v Evanston (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - EEOC v Ford Motor Company (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - EEOC v Proctor and Gamble (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - EEOC v Garland Bank (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - EEOC SAT (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Ellis v NARF (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Case Files: Ellis (cont'd) - Fuller. (Box 16)
  - Ellis v. Narf (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Farrar v. Bd. Of Public Safety (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Freeman v. Alloway (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Freeman v. Fayetteville (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Freeman United Coal (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Fuller v. Cisneros (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Friend v. Leidinger (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Case Files: Gill - Gonzalas. (Box 17)
  - Gill Facts, 48-95 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Gonzales v. Felker (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Gonzales v. Feltzer (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Case Files: Gourdino - Guardians. (Box 18)
  - Gourdine v. Ellis (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Griggs v. Duke Power (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Gray v. IBEU (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Green v. Hampstead (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Griffin v. Wainwright (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Griggs v. Duke Power (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Griggs v. Wilson Sinclair (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Greensborough, NC (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Gill Facts 1-47 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Guardians II (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Guardians III (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Guardians IV NYCPD (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Case Files: Guardians (cont'd). (Box 19)
  - Guardians I v. NYCPD (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Guardians I v. NYCPD (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Guardians II v. NYCPD (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Guardians II v. NYCPD (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Guardians III v. NYCPD (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Guardians III v. NYCPD, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Test/ Survey (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Case Files: Hall - Howard. (Box 20)
  - Hall v. Civil Service Comm. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Harmony v. NH Fire (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Harper v. Mayor and City Council of Baltimore (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Hart v. Buckeye Ind. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Hathorn v. South Central Bell (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Headen v. Cleveland (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Henderson v. 1st National Bank Montgomery (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Henderson v. Social Security (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Herbert v. Palm Beach (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Hispanic Coalition of NY v. Valenti (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Holliman v. Price (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Hispanic Soc. V. Sanit (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Howard v. Freedman (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Case Files: James. (Box 21)
  - James v. Conn. Pers. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - James v. Stockham (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - James v. Stockham Values, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - James v. Stockham (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - James v. Stockham (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - James v. Stockham Assess (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Case Files: Johnson - Kirkland. (Box 22)
  - Johnson v. City of Alabama (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Johnson v. North Carolina State Police (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Jones v. HRA (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Jones v. UGI (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Jones v. UGI (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - King v. Civil Service (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Jordan v. Wilson Montgomery (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Kinsey v. Legg Mason (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Kirkland v. Correction NY (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Case Files: Lambert - Luevano. (Box 23)
  - Lambert v. Genesee Hosp. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - League of Martin v. Milwaukee (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Lemons v. Missouri Dept. Personnel (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Louis v. Bethlehem Steel (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Tuler's Testimony: Louisville Black PO v. Louisville (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Louisville Black Police Officers Org'n v. City of Louisville (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Louisville Black PO's v. Louisville (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Luevano v. Campbell (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Case Files: Luevano (cont'd) - Miranda. (Box 24)
  - Pace (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Lugo vs. Bronstein (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Lutterlon v. NYC Housing Police (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Melendez (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Melendez v. New Mexico (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Miami PD (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Miranda (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Case Files: Moody - Macchiarula. (Box 25)
  - Moody v. Albemarle Paper (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Moraga (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Morton v. NYC Board (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Moon v. Cook County (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Munn v. Federal Paper Board Co. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Encore Macchiarola v. Board of Examiners (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Interview (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Macchiarola v. Board of Examiners (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Appendix: DDI Security Precautions (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Case Files: Macchiarula (cont'd) - New Jersey. (Box 26)
  - Development of Examinations for Principal JHS and Day HS (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Schools (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - NAACP v. Allen (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Work Motivation NYU (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - New Haven County Silver Shields v. NHORS (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - NADEAU v. Ford (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - New Haven Silver Shields (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - N.J. F.D. (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Case Files: New Jersey (cont'd) - Norris. (Box 27)
  - NJ Reports (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - NJ Bak (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - NJRD Data SSQ (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - NY Commission v. West Point Deferral (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Mcholas v. NYNEX (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Norris and Hendrix v. Glencoe (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Case Files: Northside Law - Palmer. (Box 28)
  - North State Law v. Charlotte (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - North State Law Enforcement Off. V. Charlotte (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Pace (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Palmer v. Haige (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Palmer v. Schultz Depos. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Palmer v. Schultz (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Case Files: Pandazides - Pegues. (Box 29)
  - Pandazides (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Pandazides (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Pegues v. Miss Ses (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Pegues v. Miss (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Case Files: Pegues (cont'd) - Pennsylvania. (Box 30)
  - Pegues v. Miss. SES (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - PENA v. O'Neil: Background (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Penna v. O'Neil (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Penna v. O'Neil (Validation of Promotion Exams) (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Penna v. O'Neil (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Case Files: Pennsylvania (cont'd). (Box 31)
  - Pennsylvania v. O'Neil Patrolman (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Penn. V. O'Neil Patrolman (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Penn. v. O'Neil (Promotion) (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania v. Rizzo (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Penn. Operating Engine Epilogue (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Case Files: Pennsylvania (cont'd) - Price. (Box 32)
  - Harrisburg PD (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania and Williams v. Local 542 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Petway v. Amer. Cast-iron Pipe (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Pettit v. Gingerich (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Pines v. State (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Case Files: Queen - Rodgers. (Box 33)
  - Queen v. Dresser Industries (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Republic Steel (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Richmond Black PO v. Richmond (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Rios v. Enterprise Ass'n Steamfitters (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Republic Steel (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Reeves v. Atlanta (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Rodgers v. United States Steel (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Case Files: Rodriguez - Shield Club. (Box 34)
  - Rodridges v. Denver (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Runwin (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Job Analyses: Rubinos v. Bd. Of Examiners (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Rubinos v. Board of Examiners (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Rubinos v. Board of Examiners (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Rubinos Trial Info (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Sandusky (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Schrichte v. Eastern Airlines (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Secret v. Dane County (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Shield Club v. Cleveland (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Case Files: Sims - Thompson. (Box 35)
  - Sims v. Sheet Metal Workers (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Smith v. East Cleveland (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Tax and Related Records (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Spivey v. Kaiser Alumni (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Stalworth v. Monsanto Chemical (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Stanton v. Standard Oil (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Stevenson v. International Paper (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Sweeney v. Keene State College (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Taylor v. Jordan (Jersey City FD) (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Thompson v. Regency Hyatt House (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - St. Louis (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Case Files: Timpano - United Black Firefighters Association. (Box 36)
  - Timpano v. East Ramapo School Dist. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Toledo (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - TROP World (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Tyler v. NY Civil Service (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - UBFA v. Akron (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - UBFA Dead File (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Case Files: United States Post Office - Vanguard. (Box 37)
  - USPS (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - USPS (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Vanguard v. Hughes (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - City of Baltimore Police Sergeant Assessor Manual (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Vanguard v. Hughes (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Alabama State Trooper Sergeant (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Case Files: Vanguard (cont'd) - Vulcan. (Box 38)
  - Vanguard III (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Warner Communications (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Vanguard v. Baltimore (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Vanguard MTLS for MEM Review (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Varner v. University of Rochester (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Verdell v. Koched (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Vulcan Soc. V. NYFD (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Vulcan v. New Jersey Civil Service (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Case Files: Vulcan - Weldon. (Box 39)
  - Vulcan Pioneers v. NJ (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Vulcan Society v. Yonkers (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Vulcan v. Westchester (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Wade v. Mississippi Coop. Ext. Serv. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Walls (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Warren v. Schlek (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Watkins v. Scott Paper (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Watson v. New Orleans PD (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Weldon Uptown Neighbors(Hunt) v. Penna Liquor Control Board (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Case Files: Weltman - Zimber. (Box 40)
  - Weltman v. NASA (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Wetzel and Ross v. Liberty Mutual (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Williams v. Diamond Shamrock (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Williams v. New Orleans (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Williams v. NYC Dept. of Pers. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Willoughby v. NJ State Lottery (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - York v. Alabama (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Young v. Edgcomb Steel (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Younger v. Lower Merion (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Zimber v. Rochester Linctype (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Case Files: U.S. v. Buffalo - U.S. v. Georgia Power. (Box 41)
  - U.S. v. Buffalo (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - U.S. v. Boston FD (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - U.S. v. Chicago Fire Dept. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - U.S. v. Chicago Police Dept. (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - U.S. v. Cleveland (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - U.S. v. Chicago Police (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - U.S. v. Detroit Edison (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - U.S. v. Georgia Power (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Case Files: U.S. v. Nassau County Post - U.S. v. New Jersey. (Box 42)
  - NC Post (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - NJ Dept. of Personnel (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - U.S. UNJ (FO) (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - U.S. v. NJ Descriptions (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Case Files: U.S. v. New Jersey (cont'd) - U.S. v. North Carolina. (Box 43)
  - U.S. v. NJFD (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - U.S. v. New York State Police (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - U.S. v. North Carolina Highway Control (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - U.S. v. N.C. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - U.S. v. North Carolina (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - U.S. v. North Carolina, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Case Files: U.S. v. San Francisco. (Box 44)
  - U.S. v. SF (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - San Francisco (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - SFFD (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - San Francisco (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Case Files: U.S. v. St. Louis. (Box 45)
  - St. Louis (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis Fire Dept. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Fire Captain Validation (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - U.S. v. St. Louis (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Case Files: U.S. v. St. Louis (cont'd). (Box 46)
  - U.S. v. St. Louis (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - U.S. v. St. Louis (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - U.S. v. St. Louis (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - U.S. v. St. Louis: Epilogue (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Correspondence. (Box 47)
  - Advisory Committee Meetings (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - '87 Chrono, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - 1988 Correspondence (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - OSA '84, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - 1982 Correspondence (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Correspondence. (Box 48)
  - Chronological Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Stevens (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - 1981 Chrono File (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - 1980 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Testing. (Box 49)
  - APA Professional Activities (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Bar Cerrine (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Barrett Tests Papers (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Fair Test (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Licensing and Certification Examinations (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Bar Exam (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Fair Test (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Commission (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Advisory Comm. (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - EEI Part Task Simulator (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Testing. (Box 50)
  - Georgia POST Council Test (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Fire Scenes (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - UGESP (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Personality Tests (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Testing Book (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Testing. (Box 51)
  - Tests (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Memorandums (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Reports (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Validity Generalization Reprints, etc. (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Publications. (Box 52)
  - The Japanese Mind: The Goliath Explained (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Labor Relations in Japan Today (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - ORC Equal Force Opportunity Group (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Performance Rating GNYC (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - 1981 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Civil Service Tests (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Civil Liberties (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Testing and Fair Employment (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Publications. (Box 53)
  - COORS (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Fire Dept. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - AS Factor Analysis (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Publications About Validity up to 1970 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Japan- Gen'l (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Performance Rating (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Publications Related to Validity- 1970 on (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Publications. (Box 54)
  - Articles on Testing (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Articles That Probably Will Never be Published (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - VITAE (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Problems With Tests- Less Useful Material (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Harvard Business Review (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - 1950-1959 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - 1960-1969.9 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - 1970-1979.9 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - 1980-1989.9 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Reprints, Clippings, Notes, Unpublished Manuscripts. (Box 55)
  - Psychology Reports (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Fair Employment Clippings, etc. (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, Unpublished Manuscripts, etc. Relating to Validity (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Analysis (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Analysis (Box 55, Folder 4)